孩子们  爱因斯坦说得对
kids, Einstein was right.
时间的快慢是相对参考系而定
Time moves at different speeds.
对于巴尼而言  昨晚在激情中一晃而过
To Barney, the previous night raced by in a blur.
而后  突然间
But then, all of a sudden,
时间在清醒中停滞了
time stopped.
这恐怕是我做过最坏的一次了
This might be the worst thing I've ever done.
嘿  别这么说
Hey, now.
虽说这不是你发挥最好的一次  但还是非常...
You weren't at the top of your game, but it was still pretty...
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
我居然出轨了
I just cheated on Kevin.
凯文是史上最好的男友  我真是太差劲了
He is the nicest guy ever.I'm a terrible person.
没关系
It's okay.
我们都出轨了
We both cheated.
有句俗语怎么说来着  负负得正嘛
What's that saying about two wrongs making a right?
应该是"一失足成千古恨"吧
"Two wrongs don't make a right"?
不  肯定不是这样的
No, that's not it.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
我居然出轨了
I just cheated on Nora.
我怎么能对诺拉做这种事呢  我们该怎么办
How could I do this to her? What are we gonna do?
我不知道
I don't know.
我能问你  今晚对你有意义吗
Can I ask you, did this mean anything?
当然有啦
Of course it did.
当然没啦
Of course it didn't.
你到底想听哪种  两种趋势我看都行
Which one are you looking for? I could see it going either way.
-今晚毫无意义  -毫无意义
- It meant nothing. - It meant nothing!
你怎么能说它毫无意义呢
How could you say it meant nothing?!
今晚当然意义重大
Of course it meant something!
不  它没有
No, it didn't!
它也不能  明白吗
It can't.Okay?
你有诺拉了  我也有凯文了
You're with Nora, and I'm with Kevin and...
我得走了
I have to go.
慢着  我们该如何跟他们开口
Wait, what are we gonna tell them?
绝口不提
Nothing.
天啊  我们犯了个大错
God! We made a horrible mistake.
但现在都结束了
But it-it is over now.
再提这件事只会伤害他们
There's no reason to hurt more people by talking about it.
你是叫我撒谎吗
You're asking me to lie?
我是...无所谓啦
That's... fine.
该死
Damn it.
我和诺拉明晚有个公司的游轮聚会
Nora and I have that work cruise tomorrow night.
我们都要携伴参加
We're all supposed to go together.
好的  我知道这么想实在有点离谱
Okay, I know this is thinking way, way out of the box,
但如果  先听我说完
but what if-- and hear me out--
如果我们都不去呢
we don't go?
不行
No.
我只想让这个夜晚成为历史  所以
I just want this whole night to fade into history, so
我们必须装得像什么都没发生一样
we have to act like it never happened.
我们应该去
We should go.
我是说  就在船上呆3个小时
I mean, it's a three-hour boat ride--
这么短时间能发生什么呀
what could happen?
《盖里甘的岛》是CBS上世纪60年代的喜剧
讲述因为一个3小时的航海之旅让7个人流落荒岛的故事
我打赌盖里甘会这么说
I'm sure that's what Gilligan said.
YYeTs人人影视字幕组出品
更多原创字幕翻译 请登陆www.YYeTs.com
时间轴： godwuwen 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
翻译： 一块二  非燕  阿蘅阿蘅  猫中之王 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
校对： YY    后期： 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
老爸老妈浪漫史
第七季  第十集
怀旧狂欢音乐会
Groovapalooza!
囊括上世纪90年代所有自以为是的嬉皮士乐队
All the smug hippie bands from the '90s in one big concert.
甚至门票都有一股丁香烟和庸才的味道
Ah, even the tickets smell like cloves and mediocrity.
嬉皮士常常与丁香烟联系在一起
为了重回过去的美好时光
And to really take us back,
我还特意弄来一袋  没错  就是大麻
I scored us a bag of, yes, mari...
孩子们  为了更好地感受音乐会的气氛
Kids, we used to do something before concerts
我们会在开始前做件事
to enjoy them more.
那就是  吃个三明治
And that thing was to... eat a sandwich.
加料牛肉三明治
...nated steak subs.
哦也
Oh, yeah!
我们快要为人父母了  三明治还是少吃为妙
Well, as future parents, we'll pass on the sandwiches.
你怎么能提议这种事呢  泰德
How could you even suggest such a thing, Ted?!
快把我60块还给我
I better get my 60 bucks back.
不吃三明治吗
No sandwich?
马修  这可是狂欢会呀
Marshall, it's a palooza.
以前每一个狂欢会  我们都会吃三明治
We've eaten sandwiches at every palooza.
摇滚狂欢会  爵士狂欢会
Lollapalooza, Funkapalooza...
还有大学三年级  妇女能顶半天狂欢会
Gender-diversity-awareness- palooza, junior year.
我记得  当时还有几个贱女人赶我呢
Yeah, there were some real bitches there.
好了  快点
Okay, quick,
趁莉莉没来  我们先吃掉它
before Lily gets here, let's fire this up.
不行  我答应过莉莉要有责任心
No way. I promised Lily that I would be responsible.
反正你的60块也要不回来了
You're not getting your 60 bucks back.
那还是来一口吧
Give me that.
你还好吧
Hey, how you holding up?
我要跟你们三个困在这艘船上一整晚
Well, I'm about to be trapped on a boat all night
我的戴绿帽的男友  我的出轨对象
with the guy I cheated on, the guy I cheated with
我出轨对象的戴绿帽女友
and the girl that the guy I cheated with cheated on.
所以  我一点都不好
So, not super.
你好  桑迪
Hi, Sandy.
不用谢
You're welcome.
我可没跟你道谢呀
I did not say "Thank you."
你太客气了
Oh, you're too kind.
太客气了
Too kind.
借过  我真该试过去
Excuse me, I should really try
把那个新实习生搞上床
to have sex with that new intern.
罗宾的老板桑迪·里维斯  每年都要举办这个游轮会
Robin's boss Sandy Rivers hosted this cruise every year,
主要是为了跟新员工搭讪
mostly to hit on the new employees.
而且他还想到了一个分文不花的妙招
And he'd found a clever way to never spend a cent.
接下来  亚利桑那州
Up next, another four deaths
又有4人因史上最强的热浪而致死
in Arizona's record-breaking heat wave.
你想体验真正的史上最强热辣感吗
You want real record-breaking heat?
来一杯克里托夫牌辣椒椰汁伏特加马丁尼酒
Try Kristoff's Jalapeno Coconut Vodka martini.
热辣得不得了哦[西班牙语]
Muy caliente!
好吧  诺拉和凯文随时会到
Okay, Nora and Kevin are gonna be here any minute.
我原以为我能应付得来  但现在不行
I thought I could handle this, but I can't.
好吧  那就按计划走吧
Okay, um, here's the plan.
我们随便找个救生艇  逃回岸上
We'll grab one of the lifeboats, get back to shore,
销毁我们滚床单的录像
destroy the tape of us doing it...
你居然把过程录下来了
There's a tape of us doing it?
然后我们开始一段新的人生
...and we'll start a new life together.
去一个即简单又舒适的地方  比如佛蒙特州或者迪拜
Somewhere simple and homey, like Vermont or Dubai.
等下  这是你想要的生活吗
Wait, is that what you want?
你想跟我在一起
For us to be together?
罗宾
Hey, Robin.
天啊  我真的应付不来
Oh, God, I really can't do this.
别担心  听我指挥  保持淡定
Don't worry. Just follow my lead and keep cool.
伙计们
Hey, guys!
他们知道了
They know!
完了
Oh, no.
我觉得那个三明治夹杂了其它东西
I think that sandwich was laced with other stuff.
比如超强猛料
Like, hard meats.
何出此言
What do you mean?
我一般吃完三明治后会胡思乱想  可现在没有
Well, usually after a sandwich, I feel paranoid, but I'm not.
为什么我没有胡思乱想
Why am I not feeling paranoid?!
别激动  兄弟
Calm down, dude!
没事的
We'll be fine.
莉莉会知道的
Lily's gonna know.
听我说
Listen to me.
虽然我不记得刚才我们在说什么
Whatever we were just talking about...
反正没事的
we'll be fine.
你说得对  她不会发现的
You're right, she won't find out.
伙计们
Hey, guys.
她知道了
She knows!
晚上好
Good evening.
接下来要特别欢迎我们的4位新实习生  分别是
A special welcome to our four new interns:
艾丽卡...和其他人
Erika... and so on.
安全小贴士  万一有人不幸落水
One safety matter: life preservers are on the side rails,
救生用具就在甲板两侧
in case anyone falls overboard.
我说完了  祝各位有个愉快的夜晚
That's it. Have a good night.
别喝太多哦
Don't drink too much.
喝多也无妨
Or do.
今晚真开心  是吧  同志们
Beautiful night, huh, gang?
对  我和罗宾刚在偷偷...
Yeah, Robin and I were just cheating--
讨论今天有多热
chatting about how warm it is.
我真是不忠...不中用
I'm breaking a trust-- sweat
大汗淋漓呀
in here.
我觉得我们热到要被抓去浸猪笼了
And I thought we'd be cuckold.
我知道你为什么那么紧张  巴尼
I know why you're so nervous, Barney.
你真知道
You do?
明晚你要跟诺拉的父母见面  对吧
You're meeting Nora's parents tomorrow night, right?
对对  没错
That's it! That's it!
咱们去跳舞吧
Let's dance!
莉莉不知道我嗨了
Lily has no idea I'm high.
你嗨了
You're high?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
莉莉不知道我嗨了
Lily has no idea I'm high.
好吧  如果你怀孕的妻子
Okay, well, if your pregnant wife
不得不清醒地坐在这儿一整晚
has to sit here sober all night,
那你至少得给她来点玉米片吧
she's gonna need some of them nachos.
如你所愿
You got it.
-伙计  把你玉米片交出来  -不要他吃过的
- Hey, dude, fork over some of them nach... - No, not his.
我要独享一人份
My own.
聪明
Ah. Smart.
快走  泰德
Come on, Ted.
怎么了
What?
于是我们踏上了人生最悲惨的旅程
And thus began the most harrowing journey of our lives.
迄今为止  罗宾和巴尼都发誓
To this day, Robin and Barney swear
当时他们跳舞就是放的这首歌
this is the song they danced to that night.
* 一株绿草出了墙 *
* You fooled around on your baby *
* 坦白总比隐瞒强 *
* Now the least you could do is to tell her the truth *
* 回头是岸西装男 *
* Yes, you in the suit *
* 秘密吞噬你灵魂 *
* Or that secret will eat up your soul *
* 女孩内疚到发狂 *
* Girl, the guilt's gonna drive you crazy *
* 到发狂 *
* Crazy *
* 别瞒凯文这儿郎 *
* You can't live with this lie, Kevin's such a nice guy *
* 刻不容缓就今晚 *
* Gotta tell him tonight *
* 就在此船道真相  *
* Tell them right here on this boat *
* 你如污垢般肮脏 *
* You're like scum round the edge of a toilet bowl *
* 冲光光 *
* Flush *
* 不守妇道难见光 *
* What the hell is in the place where you should have a soul? *
* 爱偷欢 *
* Slut *
* 你俩已铸成大错 *
* You did these too wrong *
* 快下决定别傍徨 *
* Don't wait too long *
* 其实何不就这样 *
* In fact, you know what? *
* 在我歌中来坦白 *
* Tell them right during this song *
* 坦白  坦白  坦白 *
* Tell 'em, tell 'em, tell 'em, tell 'em, tell 'em *
我等着
I'll wait.
* 摊牌  摊牌  摊牌 *
* Tell 'em, tell 'em, tell 'em, tell 'em, tell 'em *
拜托  你们真的不打算摊牌吗
Oh, come on, seriously, you're not gonna tell them?
我们得坦白  现在就说
We have to tell them. Right now.
* 无耻盗用我妙方 *
* Sure, act like it was your idea. *
说真的  你俩真没用
Seriously, you guys suck.
我和马修还在排队给莉莉买玉米片
Marshall and I were still in line to get Lily's nachos.
伙计  我们都等了都快一辈子了
Dude, we've been waiting forever.
更糟的是  这是等着上女厕的队伍
Even worse, this is the line for the ladies' room.
真不敢相信  我们最后一次参加狂欢会
I can't believe that our last Groovapalooza was,
是在12年前
what, 12 years ago?
我是说  时间过得真快
I mean, time is going by so fast.
我知道这很疯狂
I know, it's crazy.
就好像一眨眼
In, like, an eye blink,
这只手就会变成皱巴巴的老人手
this hand will be, like, an old man's hand.
我知道接下来我说的都是些陈词滥调  可...
I recognize the clichéd nature of what I'm about to say, but...
-哇塞  -是吧
- Whoa! -Yeah.
312?
我们就从这儿出来的
That's our gate.
伙计  我们刚把整个场地转了一圈
Dude, we just walked around the entire arena.
我们走了大约一小时
We've been walking for, like, an hour
还是没找到玉米片
and we still haven't found the nachos.
我猜莉莉一定很失望
I bet Lily is so upset.
喂  兄弟  我的玉米片分你一半
Yo, you want my nachos, bro?
谢谢
Thank you.
我丈夫出去买这玩意儿都一个小时了
My husband's been gone an hour looking for these.
如果这点事都办不好
If he can't even do that,
我怎能相信他会是个好父亲呢
how can I trust him as a father?
不可信  兄弟  不可信呀
You can't, bro. You can't.
我喜欢你长长的山羊胡
I like your long goatee.
马修连一根胡子都长不出来
Marshall can't even grow a beard.
真可怜
Oh, that's sad.
因为如果一个人脸上连根毛都不长
'Cause one's ability to grow facial hair directly correlates
那他还有毛能力做个好父亲呀
with one's ability to be a good father.
我就知道  我就知道
I know it does. I know it does.
先生  请问一下
Excuse me, sir.
你知道哪里卖玉米片吗
Do you know where the nachos are?
马修
Marshall!
过来  我找到买玉米片的队伍了
Over here. I found the nacho line.
凯文那边怎么样了
So, h-how'd it go with Kevin?
我刚准备告诉他
Well, I was just about to tell him...
听我说  凯文
Look, Kevin...
艾丽卡  我整晚一直想跟你说话
Erika, I've been meaning to speak with you all night.
是吗  想说什么
Really? What about?
说我想有一副娇躯  俯身栏杆
About me bending your hard little body over the railing
面朝纽约
of this boat and copulating furiously
"春"暖"花"开
while I admire the New York City skyline.
如果你想玩大点  我们就改朝新泽西
Or, if you're feeling dirty, we can always face Jersey.
你意下如何
Thoughts?
墨西哥辣椒
Jalapeno!
还有少许椰汁
And just a hint of coconut.
凯文撞到头了  可能是脑震荡
Kevin hit his head, he might have a concussion.
显然  我不能告诉他
So obviously I couldn't tell him.
那你呢
What about you?
她的遭遇更惨绝人寰
Something even worse happened to her.
我的袖子上有个小酒渍
I got a tiny spot of wine on my sleeve.
我不能雪上加霜
I couldn't pile on.
我又不是禽兽
I'm not a monster.
到底哪里有得卖呀
Where are they?
算了吧  别想着玉米片了
Come on, forget the nachos.
这里的人都自得其乐
Everyone here is having fun.
瞧  还包括这些人
Look, even these guys.
看看
Check it out.
音乐是连结人们的纽带
Wow, music really does bring people together.
泰德  泰德
Ted? Ted!
有个变态吉他手跟着我们
Creepy guitar guy is following us.
我们又绕了整整一圈
We did a whole nother lap.
天啊  我们差不多错过半场演唱会
Oh, man, we missed, like, half the concert now.
-我们还是回去吧  -泰德  泰德
- Come on, let's just go back to our seats. - Ted, Ted, Ted.
人们一直在这排队买玉米片呢
The nacho line was right here all along.
咱俩真笨
So stupid.
船一靠岸  我就送凯文去急诊室
As soon as we dock, I'm taking Kevin to the E.R.
天啊  真希望昨晚什么都没发生
God, I wish last night never happened.
我可不这么想
I don't.
这话什么意思
What do you mean?
如果这件事的主线
What if this whole thing,
不是在于  我们犯下弥天大错
it isn't the story of how we both made a horrible mistake
葬送了各自的感情
and ruined our relationships,
而是在于我们重修旧好呢
what if it's actually the story of how we got back together?
好吧  我最后再问你一次
Okay, I'm gonna ask you one last time.
这是你想要的结果吗
Is this what you want?
这是我们想要的结果
It's what we both want!
不然我们干嘛这么着急地想告诉他们真相
Why else are we rushing to tell them what we did?
还要在船上说  这主意太烂了
On a boat! That is a terrible idea!
巴尼  我们努力过  但最终分手收场
Barney, we tried this and we failed.
为什么还要执迷不悟呢
Why try again?
因为我总是忍不住想起你
Because I haven't stopped thinking about you
而你也没有彻底忘记我
and you haven't stopped thinking about me.
我的生活一团糟
I'm such a mess.
为什么
Why...
你为什么会喜欢我
Why do you even like me?
我想
I guess...
因为你的生活跟我一样糟
'cause you're almost as messed up as I am.
还有一个小问题
Well, there's the small issue
就是目前我们各自都有男女朋友
that we're currently dating other people.
这样如何
How about this?
船一靠岸  我们就去...做该做的事
After we dock, let's each do what we have to do,
午夜时分在麦凯伦酒吧碰面  然后
and then meet up at MacLaren's at midnight and...
正式谈谈我们自己
talk about us.
别忘了你们的神秘礼物包
Don't forget your mystery gift bags!
里面全是套套哦
They're condoms.
我们又绕了整整一圈
We just went all the way around again!
玉米片到底在哪里啊
Where the hell are these nachos?!
谁在乎玉米片啊
Who cares about nachos?
我在乎
I do.
我超爱玉米片的  伙计
Oh, I love nachos, man!
你该放松一下  伙计
You gotta relax, man.
你一直在为玉米片焦虑
You keep worrying about stuff like nachos,
这样下去你该犯心脏病了
you're gonna give yourself a heart attack.
-我要进去了  -好吧
- I'm going back in. - Fine!
哈  被耍了吧
Ha! Joke's on you!
人们一直在这排队买玉米片呢
The nacho line was right here all along!
罗宾和巴尼终于下船了
Robin and Barney are finally off the boat.
急诊室
于是他们觉得现在应该更容易
So they both assumed it was going to be a lot easier
开口坦诚他们的所作所为
to admit what they had done.
-凯文  -我先说
- Kevin... - Me first.
我不想把第一次开口说"我爱你"
Look, I don't want to make too much out
这件事弄得很夸张
of saying "I love you" for the first time...
能让我插个队先说吗
Any way I can jump in with my thing?
罗宾  我爱你
Robin... I love you.
诺拉  听我说
Okay, Nora, look...
妈  爸
Mom! Dad!
诺拉  我们提前到了
Hi, Nora, we got in early!
早知道就在船上做了断了
Should've done it on the boat.
你的朋友呢
Hey, where's your friend?
由于他罔顾我们的友情  非要去找玉米片
We missed almost the entire show because he put his stupid quest
害我们几乎错过了整场演出  所以我不管他了
for nachos ahead of our friendship, so I bolted.
我只是一个变态老吉他手
Well, I'm just a creepy old guitar player,
但和朋友在一起的每分每秒  不应该觉得幸福吗
but isn't any time spent with a friend a blessing?
如果你们一心要求玉米片
And if nachos is all you seek...
我的给你吧  兄弟
take mine, brother.
谢谢
Thank you.
这是个标牌  兄弟
It's a sign, bro.
没错
It is.
标志着我应该去找马修
It's a sign I should go find Marshall!
马修  马修
Marshall! Marshall!
巴尼  诺拉跟我们说了很多你的事
So, Barney, Nora's told us so much about you,
但我们想了解你的全部
but we want to know everything.
让我想想  喜欢西服  喜欢真人CS
Ah, let's see, suits, laser tag,
喜欢说"等一下"  自我介绍完毕
I say "Wait for it" A lot. That's about it.
你俩肯定累坏了
You two must be exhausted.
我去煮咖啡
I'll make coffee.
看到你们这么幸福  我很开心
I'm so glad to see how happy you both are.
当你遇见命中注定的那个人时
When you meet the right person,
你自然会知道
you know it.
你总会忍不住想起她
You can't stop thinking about them.
她是你的莫逆之交
They're your best friend...
也是你的灵魂伴侣
...and your soul mate.
你迫不及待要和她共度余生
You can't wait to spend the rest of your life with them.
她独一无二   无人能及
No one and nothing else can compare.
咖啡怎么还没好
Now, where the hell is that coffee, eh?
诺拉  我有话要对你说
Look, Nora, there's something I have to tell you.
有人犯心脏病了
Heart attack.
天啊   泰德说得对  我要放轻松
Oh, God, Ted was right. I have to relax!
泰德
Ted!
-马修  -泰德
- Marshall! - Ted?
-泰德  -马修
- Ted! - Marshall!
泰德啊泰德
Oh, Ted! Oh, Ted!
我很抱歉  你说得对
I'm so sorry! You were right.
不  马修  不过我是对的
No, Marshall, you... Yeah, I was right.
瞧  玉米片
But look, nachos!
走  我们进去吧
Come on. Let's go back inside.
完了
That's it.
音乐会结束了
It's over.
我们错过了整场演出
We missed the whole show.
所以
So...
没错  我爱你
Yup, I love you.
凯文
Look, Kevin...
有件事我必须告诉你
There's something I have to tell you.
我出轨了
I cheated on you.
我不知道该作何反应
I don't even know how to react.
我真的很抱歉
I am so sorry.
我明白你不会原谅我的
I know I don't get any second chances,
可你永远会是...
but you will always be...
是一夜情吗
Was this a one-time thing?
告诉我她对你来说毫无意义
Can you tell me it didn't mean anything?
不是的
No.
抱歉  泰德
I'm sorry, Ted.
我也想跟你一起找乐子
I still want to have fun,
可我也得做个好老公  当个好父亲
it's just, I have to be a good husband and father, too.
能跟你一起纵情欢乐的时间不多了
There's just not enough time, you know?
我知道
I know.
岁月如飞刀
It's all going by so damn fast.
刀刀催人老呀
We're getting old.
莉莉
Lily!
莉莉  抱歉
Hey! Oh, Lily, I'm so sorry
我们把今晚给毁了
that we ruined our night.
你们俩说什么呢
What are you guys talking about?
你们才出来不到两分钟
You've been gone less than 2 minutes.
孩子们  她没说错
Kids, she was right.
老人手
My hand.
哇塞
Whoa!
音乐会
Ah! Concert!
玉米片
Nachos! Ah!
音乐真奇妙
Haha, music!
-时光啊  -玉米片啊
- Time! - Nachos!
多谢了
Thank you!
这是个标牌  兄弟
It's a sign, bro.
-有人犯心脏病了  -马修
- Heart attack! - Marshall!
-马修  -泰德
- Marshall! Oh! - Ted! Ted!
岁月啊
Time...
-莉莉  -莉莉
- Lily! - Lily!
马修  你发现了吗
Marshall, do you get what this means?
生命还没有太匆匆
Life isn't moving too fast.
我们还来得及做任何事
We-we still have time for everything!
我们也没有错过音乐会
And we're not gonna miss the concert!
十分钟后
我快嗨爆了
I'm freaking out.
freak out也指吸毒后产生幻觉的意思
-我们得离开这儿  -没错
- We gotta get out of here. - Yeah
你们知道女厕所在哪儿吗
Do you guys know where the ladies' room is?
-不知道  -从没见过
- No idea. - Haven't seen it.
约会怎么样
Hey! How's it going?
不怎么样  我和诺拉分手了
Oh, not great. Nora and I broke up.
我的天  出什么事了
Oh, my God, what happened?
我暂时不想谈这个  不过
I don't really feel like getting into it, but...
我想我已经看见胜利的曙光了
I think the worst part is over.
-凯文  -你好  凯文
- Hey, Kev. - What's up, Kev?
还好吗  老兄
How's it going, buddy?
各位好呀
Hey, guys.
有件事我必须告诉你
There's something I have to tell you.
我不想听
Then don't.
什么
What?
作为一个心理医生  我至少学到一件事
If there's one thing I've learned as a therapist,
那就是有些"必须得说"的话
it's that just because something needs to be told
不一定就"必须得听"
doesn't always mean it needs to be heard.
凯文  我做了一件坏事
Kevin, I did something bad.
人非圣贤
We've all ne bad things.
孰能无过
Doesn't mean we're bad people.
我不在乎你过去的细枝末节
Look, I don't care about every detail from your past,
也希望你别在乎我的
and I hope you don't care about mine either.
我在乎的只是你
What I do care about is you,
从今往后  希望你跟我一样在乎这份感情
and that from tonight forward, you're in this as much as I am.
你觉得如何
What do you think?
我的生活一团糟
I'm such a mess.
你为什么会喜欢我
Why do you even like me?
过来
Come here.
你说的每一件事都让我惊喜
I am constantly amazed by the things you say,
你做的每一件事都让我着迷
entranced by the things you do,
不像某个牌子的辣椒椰汁伏特加马丁尼酒
and unlike a certain Jalapeno Coconut Vodka martini,
不会辣到让我的眼睛流泪
you're easy on the eyes.
如果我们相处再久一点
And if we're together long enough,
希望有一天  你眼中的自己就像我眼中的你一样
I hope that one day you see yourself the way I see you.
这个回答真不错
That's a pretty good answer.
时间很奇妙  有时候如白驹过隙
Sometimes hours can feel like minutes
有时候却似度日如年
and sometimes a single second can last a lifetime.
对巴尼来说  最漫长难熬的一秒莫过于此时
For Barney, the second that would never end was this one.
各位  我先走了
Well, um, I should go.
今晚真难熬
Tough night.
抱歉[对不起]
I'm so sorry.
真不用  其实没什么
Don't be. It's nothing.
恢复清醒的感觉真好
It feels good to be sober again.
天啊  我们都快在这坐到地老天荒了
Man, how long have we been sitting here, right?
你坐下也就12秒  还坐错了卡座
12 seconds and you're in the wrong booth.
我还是滚上床睡觉吧
I should go to bed.
Crooked Fingers 《Heavy Hours》
* 在你窗外  我翘首等待 *
* Outside your window I waited for you *
* 痴痴苦等  你不见芳踪 *
* You didn't come, you never do *
* 沉重的分秒 *
* Heavy hours *
* 从我的皮肤上划过 *
* Passing by away *